Finding aid to the Classes of 1891-1900 records CA.MS.01022
Smith College Archives
- Class of 1893 Records, 1886-1995; 6.958 linear feet (13 containers)
  - Class of 1893: Lists, 1928-29; 1931; 1933-34; undated (Box 1472, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1893: Monogram and Stationery (Box 1473, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1893: Reunions-General and Undated, 1893-94; 1908; 1910; 1913-14; 1918; 1921-23; 1925; 1927-28; 1933; 1938 (Box 1473, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1893: Reunions-3rd, 1896 (Box 1473, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1893: Reunions-5th, 1898 (Box 1473, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1893: Reunions-10th, 1903 (Box 1473, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1893: Reunions-15th, 1908 (Box 1473, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1893: Reunions-17th, 1910 (Box 1473, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1893: Reunions-20th, 1913 (Box 1473, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1893: Reunions-25th, 1918 (Box 1473, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1893: Reunions-30th, 1923 (Box 1473, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1893: Reunions-35th, 1928 (Box 1473, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1893: Reunions-40th, 1933 (Box 1473, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1893: Reunions-45th, 1938 (Box 1473, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1893: Reunions-50th, 1943 (Box 1473, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1893: Reunions-55th, 1948 (Box 1473, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1893: Senior Dramatics (Box 1473, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1893: Songs, undated (Box 1473, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1893: Sophomore Reception, 1889 (Box 1473, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1893: Sophomore-Senior Reception for 1891 (Box 1473, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1893: Class Supper, 1903; undated (Box 1473, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1893: Adams, Ella Maria, 1924; undated (Box 1474, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1893: Adams, Martha Rumery, 1928; 1939; undated (Box 1474, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1893: Andrus, Jessie Fish, 1928; undated (Box 1474, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1893: Ayer, Frances May (Photographs, etc), 1925; undated (Box 1474, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1893: Baker, C(aroline) Isabel (Photographs, etc), 1935; undated (Box 1474, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1893: Ball, Mina, 1890; 1923; 1928; undated (Box 1474, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1893: Barrows, Harriet Louise, 1924; 1928; 1930; undated (Box 1474, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1893: Bigelow, Harriet Williams (Box 1474, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1893: Blackstone, Martha Blackwell, 1910; 1916-17 (Box 1474, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1893: Blackstone, Martha Blackwell (Photographs, etc), undated (Box 1474, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1893: Bourland, Caroline Brown (Box 1474, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1893: Boynton, Bertha Ella (Photographs), undated (Box 1474, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1893: Bradbury, Ellen Brooks, 1889; 1924; 1928; 1933; undated (Box 1474, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1893: Bradbury, Ellen Brooks (Photographs) (Box 1474, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1893: Bradford, Stella Stevens, 1918; 1922-23; 1927-28; 1930; 1936; 1950; undated (Box 1474, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1893: Bradford, Stella Stevens (Photographs), undated (Box 1474, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1893: Bragaw, Mary, undated (Box 1474, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1893: Brewster, Anna Gertrude, 1898-99; 1903-04; 1967; undated (Box 1474, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1893: Buckingham, Grace Hammersley (Photographs), undated (Box 1474, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1893: Burgess, Mary Ellen (Photographs, etc), 1894; undated (Box 1474, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1893: Busbey, Winifred Grace (Photographs, etc), 1929; 1936; undated (Box 1474, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1893: Calhoun, Flora Jane (Photographs, etc), 1928; undated (Box 1474, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1893: Campbell, Jennie Isabel, 1924; 1928; 1933; 1935-36; undated (Box 1474, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1893: Carson, Ethel Daggett, undated (Box 1474, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1893: Carter, Edith Hovey, 1924; 1928; 1938 (Box 1474, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1893: Carter, Edith Hovey (Photographs), 1892-93 (Box 1474, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1893: Carter, Edith Hovey (Scrapbook, Photo Album), Various dates (Box 1479)
  - Class of 1893: Carter, Edith Hovey (Scrapbook, Photo Album), Various dates (Box 1479.1)
  - Class of 1893: Choate, Mary Lillian, 1963 (Box 1474, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1893: Clark, Abigail Williams, 1927; undated (Box 1474, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1893: Cook, Anna Emeline, 1918 (Box 1474, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1893: Cook, Ellen Parmelee (Box 1474, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1893: Cook, Mary A., 1928; 1932; 1935-36; undated (Box 1474, Folder 31)
  - Class of 1893: Cooper, Caroline Ella, undated (Box 1474, Folder 32)
  - Class of 1893: Copeland, Mary Emma (Photographs), 1933; 1938; undated (Box 1474, Folder 33)
  - Class of 1893: Corliss Lamont, Florence, 1938; 1940; 1983; 1995 (Box 1474, Folder 34)
  - Class of 1893: Corser, Theressa Isabel, 1938; undated (Box 1474, Folder 35)
  - Class of 1893: Crittenden, Daisy, 1890 (Box 1474, Folder 36)
  - Class of 1893: Cross, Jane P., 1933; undated (Box 1474, Folder 37)
  - Class of 1893: Darling, Frances, 1928; 1933; 1936; 1942 (Box 1474, Folder 38)
  - Class of 1893: Davis, Ina Forrest, 1928; 1939; undated (Box 1474, Folder 39)
  - Class of 1893: Denman, M(artha) Luella (Photographs), undated (Box 1474, Folder 40)
  - Class of 1893: Dole, Mary Mitchell (Photographs), 1889-90; undated (Box 1474, Folder 41)
  - Class of 1893: Dorr, Cora Louise (Photographs), 1891; 1936; undated (Box 1474, Folder 42)
  - Class of 1893: Dow, Marion Durant (Photographs), 1928; undated (Box 1474, Folder 43)
  - Class of 1893: Du Bois, Mary Susan (Photographs), 1928; 1933; 1938; undated (Box 1474, Folder 44)
  - Class of 1893: Duncan, Mabel Ticknor (Photographs), undated (Box 1474, Folder 45)
  - Class of 1893: Dwight, Julia Strong Lyman (Photographs), 1924 (Box 1474, Folder 46)
  - Class of 1893: Dyer, Josephine Tyler, 1924; undated (Box 1474, Folder 47)
  - Class of 1893: Eaton, Mary Field, 1936 (Box 1475, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1893: Emerson, Maud Lenore, 1918; 1921; 1923; 1928; 1933; undated (Box 1475, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1893: Entwistle, Antoinette (Photographs), undated (Box 1475, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1893: Estes, Jean Louise (Photographs), 1928; undated (Box 1475, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1893: Evans, Alice R., undated (Box 1475, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1893: Fales, Katharine Mildred, 1938 (Box 1475, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1893: Farr, Flora Anna, 1925; undated (Box 1475, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1893: Fay, Mary Caroline (Photographs), undated (Box 1475, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1893: Field, Elizabeth Peck, 1923 (Box 1475, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1893: Field, Grace Bowers (Scrapbook), Various dates (Box 1480)
  - Class of 1893: Field, Grace Bowers, 1928; 1933; undated (Box 1475, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1893: Flagg, Gertrude E., 1936; 1952; undated (Box 1475, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1893: Flagg, Gertrude E. (Notebook), 1900-01 (Box 1475, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1893: Frisbee, Julia Catharine, 1928; undated (Box 1475, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1893: Fuller, Violet (Photographs, etc), 1886-87; undated (Box 1475, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1893: Gamwell, Olive Wells, 1928; 1932-33; undated (Box 1475, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1893: Grant, Janet Clara (Photographs), undated (Box 1475, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour, 1890; 1927-28; 1933; 1960; undated (Box 1475, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Class Notes), 1892-93 (Box 1475, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Index), 1889-1893 (Box 1481, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Sept-Dec 1889) (Box 1481, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Jan-Jun 1890) (Box 1481, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Sept-Oct 1890) (Box 1481, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Nov-Dec 1890) (Box 1481, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Jan-Feb 1891) (Box 1481, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Mar-Apr 1891) (Box 1481, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-May-Jun 1891) (Box 1481, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Sept-Oct 1891) (Box 1481, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Nov-Dec 1891) (Box 1481, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Jan-Feb 1892) (Box 1481, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Mar-Apr 1892) (Box 1481, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-May-Jun 1892) (Box 1481, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Sept-Oct 1892) (Box 1481, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Nov-Dec 1892) (Box 1481, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Jan-Feb 1893) (Box 1481, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Mar-Apr 1893) (Box 1481, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-May-Jun 1893) (Box 1481, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1893: Hagar, Mary Lyon (Photographs, etc), 1891-93; 1925; undated (Box 1475, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1893: Hamilton, Mary Emma, 1936; undated (Box 1475, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1893: Hardy, Grace Maud (Photographs, etc), 1928; 1938; undated (Box 1475, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1893: Hartwell, Maud Appleton (Photographs, etc), 1889; 1904; undated (Box 1475, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1893: Harwood, Mary Emma (Photographs, etc), 1928; 1933; undated (Box 1475, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1893: Holden, Harriet Eleanor (Photographs, etc), 1928; 1933; undated (Box 1475, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1893: Howe, Jennie, 1925; undated (Box 1475, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1893: Hudson, Harriet Louise (Photographs, etc), 1928; undated (Box 1475, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1893: Jackson, Florence, 1892; 1903; 1925; 1928; 1933; 1936-38 (Box 1475, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1893: Jackson, Florence (Alumnae Material), 1910; 1913; 1916; 1918-28; undated (Box 1475, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1893: Jeffrey, Florence, 1936; undated (Box 1475, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1893: Johnson, Anna Louise (Photographs, etc), 1928; undated (Box 1475, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1893: Kelly, Susan Maria, 1924; 1928; 1933; undated (Box 1476, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1893: Kidder, Anna Laura (Special Student 1884-1893), 1909 (Box 1476, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1893: Knox, Susan Varick (Correspondence), 1889-1891 (Box 1476, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1893: Knox, Susan Varick (Correspondence), 1892-1893 (Box 1476, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1893: Knox, Susan Varick (Photographs, etc), 1927; undated (Box 1476, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1893: Lamson, Marion Helena (Photographs, etc), 1924; 1928; 1933; undated (Box 1476, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1893: Landon, Grace, 1920; 1923-24; 1928-29; 1933; undated (Box 1476, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1893: Landon, Grace (Photographs), 1891; 1919-21; undated (Box 1476, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1893: Landon, Mary (Photographs, etc), 1890-91; undated (Box 1476, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1893: Lane, Grace, 1939; undated (Box 1476, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1893: Leggett, Blanche Chipman, 1927; 1930 (Box 1476, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1893: Leggett, Blanche Chipman (Photographs, etc), 1933; undated (Box 1476, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1893: Lentell, Mary Althea, 1925; 1928; undated (Box 1476, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1893: Lewis, Margaret (Photographs, etc), undated (Box 1476, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1893: Libby, Blanche Edith (Photographs), undated (Box 1476, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1893: Love, Grace Mabel (Photographs), 1890; undated (Box 1476, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1893: Lyman, Virginia Dummer (Photographs, etc), 1924-25; 1928; 1933 (Box 1476, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1893: May, Margarita Britton (Photographs), undated (Box 1476, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1893: McConway, Anne, 1892; 1918; 1923-24; 1926; undated (Box 1476, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1893: Meisel, Clara Eveline, 1886; 1891; 1925; undated (Box 1476, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1893: Mills, Harriet Chidsey (Photographs, etc), 1928; undated (Box 1476, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1893: Morris, Anne Louise (Photographs, etc), 1890; 1928; 1936; 1950; undated (Box 1476, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1893: Morse, Lillian Kimball, 1924 (Box 1476, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1893: Murkland, Charlotte Marie (Photographs, etc), 1910; 1928; 1993-94; undated (Box 1476, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1893: Newell, Margaret Farrington, 1928; undated (Box 1477, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1893: Newton, M(ary) Elizabeth (Photographs, etc), 1891; 1928; undated (Box 1477, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1893: Norris, Charlotte (Photographs, etc), 1928; 1935-36; undated (Box 1477, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1893: Oakes, Margaret Maude, 1937 (Box 1477, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1893: Parker, Grace Bursley (Photographs), undated (Box 1477, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1893: Pearson, Ellen Gertrude, 1928; undated (Box 1477, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1893: Pearson, Ellen Gertrude (memorabilia book) (Box 1481.3)
  - Class of 1893: Perkins, Adelaide French, 1937; undated (Box 1477, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1893: Poole, Harriet Schoedde (Photographs, etc), 1897; 1928; undated (Box 1477, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1893: Port, Irma Genette, 1924; 1928; 1933; 1936; undated (Box 1477, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1893: Pratt, Edith Louise (Photographs), 1894; 1899; undated (Box 1477, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1893: Pratt, Laura Melancia (Photographs, etc), 1930; 1935; 1937 (Box 1477, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1893: Prentiss, Mary Ellen, 1933; 1936; 1954 (Box 1477, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1893: Presbrey, Laura Edith, 1891; undated (Box 1477, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1893: Procter, Adeline Winthrop (Photographs, etc), 1928; 1936; undated (Box 1477, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1893: Putnam, Helen Langley (Photographs, etc), 1928; undated (Box 1477, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1893: Randall, Bertha Thatcher (Photographs, etc), 1928; 1938; undated (Box 1477, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1893: Rich, Alice Elizabeth, 1914; 1923; 1928; 1931; 1933 (Box 1477, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1893: Richardson, Edith Maria, 1892; undated (Box 1477, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1893: Richardson, Mary Lincoln (Photographs, etc), 1936; undated (Box 1477, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1893: Rumsey, Olive, 1910; undated (Box 1477, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1893: Sabin, Florence Rena, 1892; 1904; 1909; 1916; 1918; 1921; 1923-26; 1929; 1931-41; 1943; 1945-46; 1960-61; 1990 (Box 1477, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1893: Sanford, Mabel Warren (Photographs, etc), 1895-96; 1903; undated (Box 1477, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1893: Scovill, Florence May, 1928; undated (Box 1477, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1893: Shepard, Bertha Maria, 1920; 1923; 1926; undated (Box 1477, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1893: Shepard, Clara Alida (Photographs), undated (Box 1477, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1893: Sherrill, Cecilia Adelaide (Photographs), undated (Box 1477, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1893: Shoemaker, Mary Erety (Photographs), undated (Box 1477, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1893: Short, Mabel Amanda (Photographs) (Box 1477, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1893: Sigsbee, Anna Lockwood, 1898; 1928; undated (Box 1477, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1893: Smith, Bertha Chester, 1890; 1923; undated (Box 1477, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1893: Smith, Caroline Frances, 1928 (Box 1477, Folder 31)
  - Class of 1893: Smith, Elisabeth, 1931; undated (Box 1477, Folder 32)
  - Class of 1893: Smith, Florence Virginia (Photographs), undated (Box 1477, Folder 33)
  - Class of 1893: Smith, Florence Virginia (Scrapbook) (Box 1481.2)
  - Class of 1893: Smith, Frances Grace (Box 1477, Folder 34)
  - Class of 1893: Soule, Elizabeth Nye (Photographs), undated (Box 1477, Folder 35)
  - Class of 1893: Sparks, Mary Estelle (Photographs), undated (Box 1477, Folder 36)
  - Class of 1893: Steele, Grace Maria, 1928 (Box 1477, Folder 37)
  - Class of 1893: Stevens, Grace Mildred (Photographs, etc), 1890-91; undated (Box 1477, Folder 38)
  - Class of 1893: Stone, Charlotte Sackett (Box 1477, Folder 39)
  - Class of 1893: Stone, Myra Josephine (Photographs), undated (Box 1477, Folder 40)
  - Class of 1893: Stratton, Lena Sophia, 1938 (Box 1477, Folder 41)
  - Class of 1893: Strong, Gertrude Helen (Photographs), undated (Box 1477, Folder 42)
  - Class of 1893: Strong, Julia Worthington, 1938; undated (Box 1477, Folder 43)
  - Class of 1893: Strong, Maud Evelyn, 1939; undated (Box 1477, Folder 44)
  - Class of 1893: Taft, Edith Lockwood (Photographs, etc), 1938; undated (Box 1478, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1893: Tapley, Elizabeth Pierce, 1924; undated (Box 1478, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1893: Thompson, Bertha Mary (Photographs), 1906; 1928; 1931; undated (Box 1478, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1893: Torr, Grace T., 1928; 1933; 1935; undated (Box 1478, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1893: Twining, Edith de Gueldry (Photographs), undated (Box 1478, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1893: Twitchell, Gertrude Marble (Photographs), undated (Box 1478, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1893: Vanderbeek, Mary Courtland (Blueprint Album, etc), 1892; 1924; 1928; 1933; undated (Box 1478, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1893: Ward, Grace, 1924; 1928; 1933; 1936; undated (Box 1478, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1893: Ward, Lily Emily (Photographs) (Box 1478, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1893: Waring, Mary Kimberley, 1894; 1900; undated (Box 1478, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1893: Watterson, Helen Mary, 1928; undated (Box 1478, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1893: Watterson, Roberta Franc, 1931; undated (Box 1478, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1893: Weeks, Imogene, 1923; 1931; 1933; 1936; 1938; undated (Box 1478, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1893: Wheeler, Frances (Photographs, etc), 1923; undated (Box 1478, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1893: Whitman, Helen Hobart, 1895; 1937; undated (Box 1478, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1893: Wilcox, Elizabeth Kenyon (Photographs), 1890; undated (Box 1478, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1893: Williams, Bessie Hastings (Photographs), undated (Box 1478, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1893: Williston, Agnes Louise, 1928; 1933; undated (Box 1478, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1893: Williston, Elizabeth (Photographs), undated (Box 1478, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1893: Wilson, Frances, undated (Box 1478, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1893: Woolen, Maria, 1928; 1933; 1967; undated (Box 1478, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1893: Wyatt, Mabel Preston, 1928; 1937-38; undated (Box 1478, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1893: Young, Emma Estelle, undated (Box 1478, Folder 23)
- Class of 1894 Records, 1823-1977; 7.208 linear feet (18 containers)
  The Class of 1894 was the sixteenth entering class and the sixteenth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class Years 1894 records, 1823-1977, contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1894. Types of materials include black and white photographs, photo albums, correspondence, letters, scrapbooks, class notes, student papers and drawings, writings, publications, newspaper clippings, record books and memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1894.
  - Class of 1894: Class Baby, 1931 (Box 1482, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1894: Class Letters, 1939-40; 1944; 1946; 1948-50; 1952-53; 1955-57 (Box 1482, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1894: Class History, Class Lists, 1948-49; 1951; undated (Box 1482, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1894: Class Photo Book (Box 1482, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1894: Class Supper (Box 1482, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1894: Commencement (Box 1482, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1894: Commencement Music (Box 1482, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1894: Commencement Photographs (Box 1482, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1894: Commencement Speaker (Box 1482, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1894: Group Photographs, 1890; undated (Box 1482, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1894: Ivy Day (Box 1482, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1894: Ivy Day Photographs (Box 1482, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1894: Junior Prom, 1893 (Box 1482, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1894: Junior Reception (Box 1482, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1894: Junior Ushers, 1893 (Box 1482, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1894: Obituaries, 1929; 1932-33; 1937; 1939; 1946-50; undated (Box 1482, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1894: Senior Dramatics (Box 1482, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1894: Senior Dramatics (Photographs) (Box 1482.1, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1894: Songs, undated (Box 1482.1, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1894: Sophomore Reception, 1890 (Box 1482.1, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1894: Unidentified Photographs, undated (Box 1482.1, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions, 1954; undated (Box 1483, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions-1895 (Box 1483, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions-1897 (Box 1483, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions-1899 (Box 1483, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions-1904 (Box 1483, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions-1909 (Box 1483, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions-1914 (Box 1483, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions-1919 (Box 1483, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions-1924 (Box 1483, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions-1925 (Box 1483, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions-1929 (Box 1483, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions-1934 (Box 1483, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions-1939 (Box 1483, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions-1944 (Correspondence with Class Secretary, Letters for Class Book) (Box 1483, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions-1944 (Box 1483, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions-1944 (Class Book typescript) (Box 1483, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions-1949 (Box 1483, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions-1954 (Box 1483, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions-1959 (Box 1483, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions-Reunion Photographs, undated (Box 1483, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1894: Reunions-Reunion Songs, undated (Box 1483, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1894: Class Secretary-Record Book, 1890-1929 (Box 1484, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1894: Correspondence with Class Secretary-1930s, 1932-35; 1937-39 (Box 1484, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1894: Correspondence with Class Secretary-1944 Jan-May (Box 1484, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1894: Correspondence with Class Secretary-1944 Jun-Dec (Box 1484, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1894: Correspondence with Class Secretary-1945-49, 1945-1949 (Box 1484, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1894: Correspondence with Class Secretary-1950 (Box 1484, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1894: Correspondence with Class Secretary-1951-54, 1951-1954 (Box 1484, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1894: Correspondence with Class Secretary-Miscellaneous, undated (Box 1484, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1894: Alumnae Council Reports, 1931-37; 1939-41; 1946; 1948; undated (Box 1484, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1894: Alumnae Fund Letters, 1943-45; 1947-48; 1951-54 (Box 1484, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1894: Treasurer's Records-Correspondence, 1949-1951 (Box 1484, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1894: Treasurer's Records-Ledger Book, 1890-1951 (Box 1484, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1894: Allen, Sarah Theodosia (Photographs), undated (Box 1485, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1894: Anderson, Grace Estey (Correspondence, etc), 1891; 1895; 1949; 1958; undated (Box 1485, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1894: Andrews, Katharine Hannah (Correspondence), 1952; undated (Box 1485, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1894: Andrews, Katharine Hannah (Photographs, etc), 1925; 1958; undated (Box 1485, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1894: Atwood, Alice Chapman, 1896; 1945; undated (Box 1485, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1894: Balch, Mary Elizabeth (Photographs), undated (Box 1485, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1894: Bancroft, Frances Marsh, undated (Box 1485, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1894: Bauer, Olive Mary (Photographs), undated (Box 1485, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1894: Bawden, Sarah Elisabeth (Photographs) (Box 1485, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1894: Brown, Inez (Photographs) (Box 1485, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1894: Brown, Ophelia Sanger (Photographs), undated (Box 1485, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1894: Browne, Frances Eliza (Correspondence), 1954 (Box 1485, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1894: Browne, Helen Swale (Photographs) (Box 1485, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1894: Browne, Helen Swale (Photographs) (Box 1485, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1894: Burrington, Venila Spaulding (Correspondence), 1950; 1954 (Box 1485, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1894: Chapman, Elizabeth Kimball (Correspondence), 1954; undated (Box 1485, Folder 16)